mhvillage.com 2008-12-17

# MHVillage.com - Privacy Policy

MHVillage.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how MHVillage.com treats personal information that MHVillage.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of MHVillage.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MHVillage.com does not own or control, or to people that MHVillage.com does not employ or manage. 

### Information Collection and Use

MHVillage.com collects personal information when you register with MHVillage.com, when you use MHVillage.com products or services, and when you visit MHVillage.com pages or the pages of certain MHVillage.com partners. MHVillage.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, address, email address, zip code and other information. Once you register with MHVillage.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

MHVillage.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of services that we offer. MHVillage.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MHVillage.com cookie information, and the page you request. MHVillage.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve our services, to contact you, to conduct research, and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

MHVillage.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MHVillage.com. These companies may use your personal information to help MHVillage.com communicate with you about offers from MHVillage.com and our marketing partners. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MHVillage.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if MHVillage.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MHVillage.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

MHVillage.com may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. MHVillage.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. MHVillage.com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

### Cookies

MHVillage.com may set and access MHVillage.com cookies on your computer. MHVillage.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MHVillage.com's cookies. 

MHVillage.com uses web beacons to access MHVillage.com cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with MHVillage.com products and services. 

### Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information

You can edit or delete your MHVillage.com Account Information at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MHVillage.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MHVillage.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your MHVillage.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

MHVillage.com may update this policy without notice from time to time, so you should check this page frequently. 

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: 

MHVillage.com  
Customer Service  
3215 Eaglecrest Drive   
Grand Rapids, MI 49525   
(616) 363-8454  
CustomerService@MHVillage.com
